

CONTACT DETAILS

- Indore, India
- □ shubhipuntambekar.netlify.app
- M https://medium.com/@shubhipun
- in linkedin.com/in/shubhipuntambekar
- 91 9424051980

EDUCATION

RGPV, BHOPAL

Bachelors of Engineering Information Technology 2018, CGPA: 7.95

CODING PROFILES

GITHUB

github.com/shubhipuntambekar

LEETCODE

https://leetcode.com/shubhipuntambekar

SKILLS SUMMARY

- ••• AWS
- •••• Python
- •••• Java
- •••• Ela<u>sticSearch</u>
- •••• Redis
- •••• Microservice Architecture
- •••• Serverless
- •••• Cloudwatch
- •••• Github
- •••• Kafka
- •••• Spring Boot
- •••• Android

AWARDS

- ABOVE AND BEYOND (Delhivery)
- DIVERSITY AND INCL. TEAM
 OF QUARTER Q4FY19
 (Zensar)

SHUBHI PUNTAMBEKAR

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a FullStack Developer with holistic knowledge of software development and design. I have an experience of 4+ years in the Internet, IT and Fintech Industry. I see myself contributing to society by engineering impactful products.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Developer

Yubi | February 2023 - Present

- Created an application to bring down the credit appraisal process time from around 7 business days to 3 hours.
- Worked on multiple credit verticals and delivered critical features on time.

Senior Software Developer

Delhivery | September 2020 - February 2023

- Developed and led revenue-critical stories for business.
- Owned and developed multiple micro-services from scratch most of which involved payment services.
- Optimised heavy traffic lambdas to decrease the iterator age by adopting scalable approaches.
- Created on-boarding and self KYC service for new users.

Software Engineer

Zensar | July 2018 - March 2020

- Worked on enhancing and maintaining products in the retail and insurance verticals.
- Contributed in creating internal products for automation.

INTERNSHIPS

Armentum Campus Training

Web Development | Jan 2018 - June 2018

Bitbytes Software Technology Pvt. Ltd.

Mobile App Development | June 2017 - September 2017

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Mobile Application | Seekho

E-Learning app providing knowledge in short 1-minute videos

Android Application | MedicoDeals

B to B E-commerce app for medicine market

Mobile Application | Food Ordering System

Food ordering app for small joints to manage their orders